{
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "characters",
      "question": "Who is the famous Wookiee co-pilot of the Millennium Falcon?",
      "answer": "Chewbacca"
    },

    {
      "type": "characters",
      "question": "What character is a protocol droid fluent in over six million forms of communication?",
      "answer": "C-3PO"
    },

    {
      "type": "characters",
      "question": "Who is the Sith Lord who was once a Jedi Knight named Anakin Skywalker?",
      "answer": "Darth Vader"
    },

    {
      "type": "characters",
      "question": "Who is the Jedi Master who trained Anakin Skywalker?",
      "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi"
    },

    {
      "type": "characters",
      "question": "Who was the Jedi Master that discovered the secret to eternal life through the Force?",
      "answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn"
    },

    {
      "type": "planets",
      "question": "What desert planet is the home of Anakin Skywalker and Luke Skywalker?",
      "answer": "Tatooine"
    },

    {
      "type": "planets",
      "question": "What is the name of Princess Leia's home planet, which was destroyed by the Death Star?",
      "answer": "Alderaan"
    },

    {
      "type": "planets",
      "question": "What lush, green planet is the home planet of Padm√© Amidala?",
      "answer": "Naboo"
    },

    {
      "type": "quotes",
      "question": "Finish this iconic line from Princess Leia: \"Aren't you a little short for a...\"",
      "answer": "\"...Stormtrooper?\""
    },

    {
      "type": "quotes",
      "question": "Who said, \"I have brought peace, freedom, justice, and security to my new empire\"?",
      "answer": "Anakin Skywalker"
    }

  ]
}